Nothing this fabulous could last forever
Studio 54 is a documentary film directed by Matt Tyrnauer.
Studio 54 was the epicenter of 70s hedonism - a place that not only
redefined the nightclub, but also came to symbolize an entire era.
Its co-owners, Ian Schrager and Steve Rubell, two friends from Brooklyn, seemed to come
out of nowhere to suddenly preside over a new kind of New York society.
Now, 39 years after the velvet rope was first slung across the club's hallowed threshold, a
feature documentary tells the real story behind the greatest club of all time.
Self, played by Ian Schrager.
Self (archive footage), played by Steve Rubell.
Self, played by Donald Rubell.
Self (archive footage), played by Michael Jackson.
Self (archive footage), played by Farrah Fawcett-Majors.
Self (archive footage), played by Liza Minnelli.
Studio 54 is a 2018 American documentary film directed by Matt Tyrnauer, examining the meteoric history
of the Studio 54 nightclub, an extravagant disco venue infamous for hedonistic excess.
Those responsible for the club's wild success reflect
on the scene they sparked in 1977.
Discotheque co-owner Ian Schrager recounts his role at the center of it all,
including the club's fraudulent accounting and legal consequences.
The film explores themes of nightclub, disco, discotheque.